Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      - G
        - Guy - The future, 1990; SR-16558; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA 10115; A-side Matrix # MCA-10388-HF1
        - Guy - Groove me (extended version), 1988; SR-16559; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA-23852; A-side Matrix # MCA-7945-FW1
        - Guy - I like (extended version), 1989; SR-16560; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # MCA-23927; A-side Matrix # MCA 8580FDS-4
        - Guy - Groove me (extended version), 1988; SR-16561; Guy (Box 286)
          Catalog # L33-17581; A-side Matrix # MCA8021FDS-1
          Uptown Records
        - Guy Called Gerald - Voodoo ray, 1988; SR-16562; Guy Called Gerald (Box 286)
          Catalog # WAR-038; A-side Matrix # WAR038A
          Warlock Records
        - Gyamfi, Rex - Hi-life for you, 1985; SR-16563; Gyamfi, Rex (Box 286)
          Catalog # DRV 001; A-side Matrix # DVR 001-A
          Dream Village Records
        - Gypsy Lane - Cold fire, 1982; SR-16564; Gypsy Lane (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16565. Different discs.
          Catalog # SPV 62; A-side Matrix # SPV-62-A
        - Gypsy Lane - Cold fire, 1982; SR-16565; Gypsy Lane (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16564. Different discs.
        - Gyrl - Play another slow jam, 1995; SR-16566; Gyrl (Box 286)
          Catalog # LSJ8P-3417; A-side Matrix # LSJ 12316-FDS1
        - Gyrl - Play another slow jam, 1995; SR-16567; Gyrl (Box 286)
        - Gyrlz - Wishing you were here, 1988; SR-16568; Gyrlz (Box 286)
          Catalog # V-15311; A-side Matrix # V-1-15311-101167/67A/67B-Z1
        - Gyrlz - If it's games you're playing, 1988; SR-16569; Gyrlz (Box 286)
          Catalog # V-15401; A-side Matrix # V-1-15401-101212B-Z1
        - GZA - Cold world, 1995; SR-16570; GZA; Genius (Box 286)
          Catalog # PRO-A-4806; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-4806-A-GL2
        - GZA - Cold world, 1995; SR-16571; GZA; Genius (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16572. Different discs.
        - GZA - Liquid swords, 1995; SR-16572; GZA; Genius (Box 286)
          In same jacket as # SR-16571. Different discs.
        - GZA - Cold world, 1995; SR-16573; GZA; Genius (Box 286)
        - Gales, Stephen - Motherlode, 1983; SR-30850; Gales, Stephen; Cheek, Wyatt (Box 302)
          Catalog # WS83-24K-SSW; A-side Matrix # WS83 24K-SSW-A
          Prolific Hot Wax
        - Gamble, Dee Dee Sharp - Dee Dee, 1980; SR-30851; Gamble, Dee Dee Sharp (Box 302)
          In same jacket as # SR-30852. Different discs.
          Catalog # JZ 36370; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AL-36370-2AA
          Philadelphia International Records
        - Gamble, Dee Dee Sharp - Breaking and entering, 1980; SR-30852; Gamble, Dee Dee Sharp (Box 302)
          In same jacket as # SR-30851. Different discs.
          Catalog # AS 918; A-side Matrix # P.I.R. AD-XSS-168471
        - Garfield - Party of love, 1995; SR-30853; Garfield (Box 302)
          Catalog # 577 307-1; A-side Matrix # 577 307-1-A
          Metronome
          Hamburg, Germany
        - Gaye, Marvin - Let's get it on, 1973; SR-30854; Gaye, Marvin (Box 302)
          Catalog # T 329V1; A-side Matrix # T 329V1-CSRS-7950-1 12B
          Detroit, Michigan
        - Gene Loves Jezebel - Shaving my neck, 1982; SR-30855; Gene Loves Jezebel (Box 302)
          Catalog # SIT 18T; A-side Matrix # SIT 18T 11
        - Gibbs, Joe and Professionals - Justice & rights; Equal rights style, 1976; SR-30856; Gibbs, Joe; Professionals; Joe Gibbs & The Professionals; Brown, Dennis; Big Youth (Box 302)
          Catalog # DSR-3638; A-side Matrix # DSR-3638-A KMJG
          Joe Gibbs Record Globe
          Kingston, Jamaica
        - Giorgia - Prende al cuore, 1988; SR-30857; Giorgia (Box 302)
          Catalog # CGD 20721; A-side Matrix # GC 80781-1L-10-8-88-B-
          CGD
          Milan, Italy
        - Girls Can't Help It - Pure wild, 1983; SR-30858; Girls Can't Help It (Box 302)
          Catalog # 1-23966; A-side Matrix # 1-23966-A-SH2 0 B-18489-SH2 SLM
        - G.L.O.B.E. - The millions; He can feel, 2000; SR-30859; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E. (Box 302)
          Catalog # BKT-2358; A-side Matrix # BKT 2358 A (RECUT)
          Breakthru Records
        - G.L.O.B.E. - The millions; He can feel, 2000; SR-30860; G.L.O.B.E.; MC G.L.O.B.E. (Box 302)
        - Gold, Brian and Tony - Sound ting, 1991; SR-17631; Gold, Brian and Tony (Box 302)
          Catalog # SIR085; A-side Matrix # SIR-085-A SOUND THING
          Two Friends Records
        - Gong - Shamal, 1975; SR-30861; Gong (Box 302)
          Catalog # V 2046; A-side Matrix # 28 V2046 A1
          London, England
        - Goody Goody - Let me work on you, 1982; SR-30862; Goody Goody; Montana, Vincent, Jr. (Box 302)
          Catalog # PSW-8882; A-side Matrix # PSW-8882
          Philly Sound Works
          Cherry Hill, New Jersey
        - Graeme Edge Band - Kick off your muddy boots, 1975; SR-30863; Graeme Edge Band; Gurvitz, Adrian (Box 302)
          Catalog # THS 15; A-side Matrix # XZAL-13750 PP
          Threshold
        - GrandMixer DXT - Megamix II: why is it fresh?, 1984; SR-30864; GrandMixer DXT; DST (Box 302)
          Catalog # CEL 173; A-side Matrix # A- CEL-173-A
        - Grant, Chuck - Can't let go, 1980; SR-30865; Grant, Chuck (Box 302)
          Catalog # LR 0001 A; A-side Matrix # LR-0001-A
          Lor Jon Records
        - Grant, Eddy - Living on the front line, 1978; SR-30866; Grant, Eddy (Box 302)
          Catalog # AS 730; A-side Matrix # XSS-166887-1A
        - Gregg Peters Band - "The king" on long play, 1981; SR-30867; Gregg Peters Band (Box 302)
          Catalog # R&R #1003; A-side Matrix # RR 1003 A
          Reelin & Rockin Records
          Brooklyn, New York
        - Grêmio Recreativo Escola De Samba Mocidade Independente De Padre Miguel - Padre Miguel vol. II, 1989; SR-23033; Grêmio Recreativo Escola De Samba Mocidade Independente De Padre Miguel; G.R.E.S. Mocidade Independente De Padre Miguel; Padre Miguel (Box 302)
          Catalog # 530.0004; A-side Matrix # 530.0004-A
          Top Tape
        - Grêmio Recreativo Escola De Samba Mocidade Independente De Padre Miguel - Bateria nota 10 - vol. 4, 1974; SR-23034; Grêmio Recreativo Escola De Samba Mocidade Independente De Padre Miguel; G.R.E.S. Mocidade Independente De Padre Miguel; Padre Miguel (Box 302)
          Catalog # TT-061; A-side Matrix # TT-061-A
        - Groove B Chill - Hip hop music, 1990; SR-30868; Groove B Chill (Box 302)
          Catalog # 75021 8085 1; A-side Matrix # 75021-8085-1-A-ES2
        - Groove Control - Beautiful, 2000; SR-17632; Groove Control (Box 302)
          Catalog # XTQT 20; A-side Matrix # XTQT-20-A
          Extatique
        - Gap Band - I don't believe you want to get up and dance (oops, up side your head), 1979; SR-30939; Gap Band (Box 147)
          Catalog # MK-127; A-side Matrix # MK-127-A 1-1-1
        - Griffin, Reggie - Whisper (in your ear); B mice elf, 1981; SR-30940; Griffin, Reggie (Box 147)
          Catalog # SM-601; A-side Matrix # VID-711-A
          Sweet Mountain Records